(Howard:)I spend my days
(Howard:)trying to take
(Howard:)ideas and make them real.
(Sheldon:)Well said, old chap.
I thought eloquence had died;
here it stands before us.
Starting today, it'll go:
Gettysburg Address,
"I have a dream"
and what you just said.
(Leonard:)Oh, now he's a genius?
(Leonard:)All you ever do is make fun
of him and engineering.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, please.
His mother just died.
(Leonard:)You're being ridiculous.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, so are you.
(Penny:)Guys, if I wanted to hear
people be bitchy,
(Penny:)I'd go to my real salon.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, lots of people
could've had that idea,
(Sheldon:)but very few people could've
(Sheldon:)worked out the math
the way I did.
(Sheldon:)Lots of people
also didn't have that idea,
(Leonard:)like everyone in the entire
world except for me.
(Sheldon:)Oh, well,
apparently Leonard thinks
(Sheldon:)he's better than everyone
in the whole world,
(Sheldon:)including those
(Sheldon:)fighting for our freedom.
(Howard:)Yeah, well,
I don't know about you,
(Sheldon:)but I support our boys overseas.
(Amy:)And girls.
Hey, you already ruined Thor;
give it a rest.
(Leonard:)So I'm just supposed to be okay
(Leonard:)with you hogging
all the credit?!